Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Constituents, 1976-1985; 3
  - Alpha Files, 1976-1985; 1
    - Government Contractors product liability (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Government Contractors product liability (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Graduation announcements, 1983-1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Hallmark cards, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Heritage Foundation, German-American Inter-Parliamentary Exchange, 1983 July 19 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Hershey, PA, Travel, 1983 November (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Hustler Magazine, Larry Flynt Publications, 1983-1984 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Industrial development bonds, 1983 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Insurance, H.R. 100, 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Internship program for 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Jacksonville District Office, 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Japanese/American legislation, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Jaycees Foundation, Hall of Leadership, 1983-1985 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. 75th Birthday celebration, Wright Patman room dedication, LBJ Library, 1983 August (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Kiwanis International, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Lobbying, Network Television Syndication, 1983 May (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, TX, General (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, TX, General (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Marshall, TX, General (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Martin Luther King National Holiday, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Classroom, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - President’s Commission on Executive Exchange, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Railroad Retirement, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Regulatory Reform, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Sabine River Authority, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Company, Gifts, 1983-1984 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Service Academy Appointment, 1983-1984 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Social Security, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - State of the Union, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Steel Pipe and Tube Arrangement Enforcement Act, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Rates Legislation, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Texas Association of Broadcasters, 1983-1984 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Texas Finance Association Convention, 1983-1984 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Texas Seal, Cast Bronze, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Turner Broadcasting System, 1983-1985 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce, 1983-1984 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Universal Telephone Service Preservation Act, H.R. 4102 (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Universal Telephone Service Preservation Act, H.R. 4102 (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Universal Telephone Service Preservation Act, H.R. 4102 (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1983-1984 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Weapon System, Booklet, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Agricultural Yearbooks, 1984-1988 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Congressional Breakfast, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - B-1B Aircraft Rollout, Palmdale, CA, 1984 August-September (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Bank Reform, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Barksdale Air Force Base Tour, Shreveport, LA, 1984 July-August (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, Mondale-Ferraro, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Funds, Misuse, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Practices Survey, U.S. News & World Report, 1984 February (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Celeste, TX, General, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Celebration, President Harry S. Truman, 1984 May 8 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Clark, General Bruce (retired), Honor and the Military, 1984-1985 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Caucus for Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Democratic National Committee Small Business Dinner, 1984 January (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1984 May-July (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Rally for Don Buford, 1984 January (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Drug Price Competition and Patent Term Restoration Act, H.R. 3605, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Durable Medical Equipment, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Educational Requests, Dr. Mitchell Young, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Farm Credit Act, Federal Land Bank Association class action suit, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Farmers Credit System, Complaints, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Federal Trade Commission Authorization Act, H.R. 2970 (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Federal Trade Commission Authorization Act, H.R. 2970 (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Howard International Gospel Hour, Letterhead Clearance, 1984 May-June (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Internship program for 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson Junior High Awards Day, 1984 May 18 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Laos, Agent Orange, Travel, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Lone Star Steel, 1984 March 23 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Longshoremen’s and Harbor Worker’s Compensation Act, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, TX, General, 1984-1985 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Medicare, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Natural Gas, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Paris Department of Human Resources, 1984 September (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Candidates, Research, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Classroom, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Realtor Issues, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Sabine Mining Company Open House, Dragline Dedication, Hallsville, TX, 1984 June 23 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - School Prayer, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Service Academy Appointment, 1984-1985 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Sledgehammer Rule, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Tax Bill, H.R. 4242, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Texas Finance Association Meeting, 1984 August 10 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Wadley Hospital, Texarkana, TX, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Visa Denials, Committee on Immigration and Nationality Law, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Farm Credit Act, 1985 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Farm Credit Act, H.R. 1217, Federal Land Banks, Reports, 1985 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Farm Credit Act, H.R. 1217, General, 1985 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Farm Credit Act, H.R. 1217, Agriculture Committee Hearing, 1985 March 26 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Farm Credit Act, Holman, et al v. Farm Credit Administration, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Farm Credit Act, Printed Material, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Farm Credit Act, Ernest Wittenberg Associates, Inc., 1985 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Farm Credit Act, H.R. 1217, “Dairy File”, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Farm Credit Act, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Farm Credit Act, Restoration Act, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Historical Deficit Comparison, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Profile, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Inauguration (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Presidential Inauguration (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Affairs, National Association of State Directors “Special President’s Award,” Recipient, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Recognitions, 1984; 2
    - Anniversaries, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Birthdays, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Congratulations, Congress, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Congratulations, General, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Congratulations, Veterans, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - District Industry, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Lone Star Ammunitions Plant, Changing of the Guard, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Regrets, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Retirements, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - Project Cards, 1976-1977; 3
    - Bowie County (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Bowie County (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Camp County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Cass County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Cherokee County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Delta County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Fannin County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Franklin County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Harrison County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Henderson County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Hopkins County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Lamar County, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Marion County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Morris County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Panola County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Red River County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Rusk County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - San Augustine County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Shelby County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Titus County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Upshur County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Wood County, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Arkansas, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - California, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Indiana, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Louisiana, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Maryland, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Missouri, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - North Carolina, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Texas, 1976-1977 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box 167, Folder 20)
- District, 1964-1986, undated; 4
  The District series, dated 1964-1986, is reflective of activities that took place in Congressman Hall’s home district. He maintained district offices in both Paris and Marshall, TX. This series contains material from both locations and is divided into three subseries, Correspondence, City and County Projects, and Publications.
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically by subject and reflects topics that were of importance in the district. The subseries is dated 1968-1986. Dates prior to 1976 are reflective of projects carried over from Hall’s predecessor, Wright Patman. Some files have been restricted due to their personal content; contact an archivist for further information.
  City and County Projects are arranged alphabetically by county, then further divided by city. These files are followed by requests from out of district, then out of state. The bulk of items are dated 1975-1985, but some requests appear as early as 1964 and are projects passed on from the tenure of Wright Patman.
  Publications is comprised of a student created magazine, Loblolly. This magazine contains oral histories collected and transcribed by students from Gary High School in Gary, Texas. Most stories cover the life and times of Panola County in the East Texas area. The magazines are ordered chronologically from 1974-1977.
  - Correspondence, 1968-1986, undated; 1
    - Bowie County, undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Caddo Lake, Wright Patman Files, 1968-1969 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Post Office Histories, by County, 1968 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Caddo Lake, Wright Patman Files, 1970-1971 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Red River, Wright Patman Files, 1970 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Congratulations, 1976-1980 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Marshall Reservoir, 1976-1977 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Resource Conservation Development Project, 1976-1979 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Caddo Lake, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Corps of Engineers, Processing Permit Times, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee Report, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Employment Request, 1977-1981 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence (2 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Highways, Streets and Bridges, 1977-1980 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Jonesville Election Returns, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Pine Creek, 1977-1978 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Shelby County History, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Shreveport to Daingerfield Reach, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Small Business Administration, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Small Business Administration, Employment Issue, 1977-1978 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Texas Department of Community Affairs, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Vitamin B6, 1977-1981 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - “Trucker of the Year”, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Caddo Lake, 1978 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Coal Production Laws, 1978 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Cooper Lake (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Cooper Lake (2 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Corps of Engineers, 1978-1979 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - East Texas Legal Services, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Federal Disaster Assistance Administration, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Henderson County Community College, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Service, 1978-1979 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Bowie County, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cherokee County, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Delta County, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Harrison County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Henderson County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Lamar County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Marion County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Rusk County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Shelby County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Wood County, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Human Development Services (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Human Development Services (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Jacksonville Baptist College, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Jarvis Christian College, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Overton Housing Authority, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Postal (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Postal (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Red River, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Small Business Administration, Disaster Assistance, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Wadley Hospital Strike, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Wiley College, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Wright Patman Lake, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - Clippings, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - General, 1979-1980 (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - Agriculture, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Banking, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Buses, Trailways, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Caddo Lake, 1979-1980 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Caddo Lake Compact, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Cars, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Carthage Cup Company, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Census Bureau, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Clinch River Breeder Reactor Project, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Conservation and Recreation Service, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Continental Telephones of Texas, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Corps of Engineers, Lake Projects, General, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Councils of Government (COG), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Department of Education (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Department of Education (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Department of Energy (1 of 7), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Department of Energy (2 of 7), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Department of Energy (3 of 7), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Department of Energy (4 of 7), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Department of Energy (5 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Department of Energy (6 of 7), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Department of Energy (7 of 7), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Department of Intergovernmental Affairs, Martin, Larry W. (RESTRICTED), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Emergency Medical Service, 1979-1980 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Energy, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Energy Showcase Program Grants, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1979 May- 1980 September (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration (2 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Farmers Home Administration (3 of 3), 1979-1983 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Four States Fair, 1979-1980 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - General, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services, 1979-1980 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Health and Human Services, 1979-1980 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Highways, Streets, and Bridges, 1979-1980 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Homeowners of Marshall, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 1-15 (RESTRICTED), 1979 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 21-45 (RESTRICTED), 1979 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 46-55 (RESTRICTED), 1979 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 56-60 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1980 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Fannin County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Franklin County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Hopkins County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Morris County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Panola County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Rains County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Red River County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Housing and Urban Development, St. Augustine County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Titus County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Upshur County, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Human Development Corporation, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Immigration & Naturalization Service, 1979-1981 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Insurance Companies, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - IRS-Cases 1-16 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1980 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - IRS-Cases 17-31 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1981 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Justice Department Cases 1-10 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1980 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Labor Cases 1-16 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1981 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Law Enforcement Alliance of America 1-6, 1979-1980 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Lon Morris College, 1979 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Meat and Poultry Inspection Office, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Mt. Pleasant Pittesburg Freight (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Mt. Pleasant Pittesburg Freight (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - National Health Insurance Program, 1979-1980 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Panola Junior College, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Pine Creek, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Small Business Administration, 1-18 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1980 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Small Business Administration, 19-39 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1981 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Small Business White House Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Tiller, Francis, 1979-1982 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Army, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Caddo Lake, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Caddo Lake, Marshall Hearing, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Central East Texas Alliance (CETA), 1980 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Community Services Administration (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Community Services Administration (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Community Services Administration (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Cemetery, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Cooper Lake, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Corps of Engineers (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Corps of Engineers (2 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Corps of Engineers (3 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Crime, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Deep East Texas Council of Governments, 1980 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Defense, 1980 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Department of Education, 1980-1981 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Department of Energy (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Department of Energy (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Department of Energy (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Department of Health Education and Welfare (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Department of Health Education and Welfare (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - East Texas Council of Government, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Medical Services, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Energy (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Energy (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1980 October- 1981 July (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Farmers Home Administration (1 of 7), 1980 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Farmers Home Administration (2 of 7), 1980 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration (3 of 7), 1980 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Home Administration (4 of 7), 1980 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Farmers Home Administration (5 of 7), 1980 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration (6 of 7), 1980-1982 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration (7 of 7), 1980-1983 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Disaster Assistance, 1980-1984 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Federal Funds to Fight Buffalo Gnats, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Agent, East Texas Adult Education Cooperative, 1980-1981 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1980-1981 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - General Services Administration, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Hall Texas Delegation, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Health and Human Services (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Health and Human Services (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Health and Human Services (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Health and Human Services (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Health and Human Services, 1980 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Highways, 1980 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 61-79 (RESTRICTED), 1980 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 80-90 (RESTRICTED), 1980 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cases 91-104 (RESTRICTED), 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Cass County, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Law Enforcement Alliance of America (LEAA) Meeting in Texarkana, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Legal Services, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Justice Department, Cases 1-10 (RESTRICTED), 1979-1980 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Office of Energy Related Inventions (Department of Commerce), 1980 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Panola Junior College, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Small Business Administration, Cases 108-122 (RESTRICTED), 1980-1983 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Texarkana Community College, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Texas Department of Human Resources, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Postal Service, 1-49, 1980 (Box 187, Folder 1)